eareview.net 2018-11-19

# Privacy Policy

The eareview.net website is operated by Birt Ltd. who may also operate other websites. It is a strict company policy to respect your privacy regarding any information that may be collected while the website is operated and while the software products available are commercialized and licensed. None of the information collected is shared with any third parties except as described below.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Birt Ltd. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Birt’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how the eareview.net visitors use the website. On rare occasions, Birt Ltd. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, for example by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the website.

The website may use cookies in order to provide a better browsing experience. Any website visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the eareview.net website, with the drawback that some features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is used to track visitors on this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data, please see the Google [data processing amendment](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/dpa/dataprocessingamendment_20130906.html) for more information.

The data collected by Birt Ltd. is only processed anonymously and “Data sharing” is disabled.

No other Google services are used in combination with the Google Analytics cookies except Google Tag Manager, used for facilitating the process of integrating Google Analytics with the eareview.net website.

### Website Forms

When you submit a support question or a request via the contact form we collect your name (when provided), the IP address and the email address so that we can correspond with you.

When posting a comment on the website, the name and email provided are recorded as well as the IP address that was used to post the comment. This information is recorded for the purpose of preventing spam, abuse and inflammatory comments.

### Software Trial

When you submit a request to sign up for a trial we collect the name (when provided), the email address and the originating IP address. This information is used to provide access to the trial by means of an email message containing the trial license key. The information is also used for validating support tickets (which can only be opened by users with an active trial or with an active support subscription) and for communicating with you, should such a support interaction be initiated. The IP address recorded may be used to identify attempted abuse.

### Software Licensing

The software distributed by eareview.net (the Tick Data Suite) is using a DRM scheme based on a license server. The software makes periodic connections to the license server for the purpose of authenticating the state of the license key; for such requests the license key and the originating IP address is recorded, together with a hashed hardware ID of the machine that is running the software. This information may be used by Birt Ltd. in determining attempted abuse of the licensing system. The hashed hardware ID cannot be used to identify any specifics of the hardware that the software is running on; it is only used to prevent repeated trials on the same machine and to prevent installing a single retail license on multiple machines.

### Newsletter

When signing up for a trial, you are also prompted to sign up for the newsletter. Should you enable the option that indicates you wish to receive the newsletter, you will receive a sign-up confirmation email and you must visit the link provided in the email in order to confirm your newsletter subscription.

When purchasing an eareview.net product you may be added to the newsletter dedicated to the customers. In this case, you will also receive a sign-up confirmation email containing a link that you must visit in order to confirm your subscription.

The eareview.net newsletters are handled by AWeber and for this purpose the name and email provided during the trial signup or during the ordering process will be recorded by AWeber. AWeber is fully compliant with GDPR as well as certified with the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield; for more information please read the [AWeber Privacy Policy](https://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm).

### Electronic Commerce

The eareview.net software is commercialized by the online retailers Digital River (MyCommerce Share-it) and Clickbank. When you make a purchase, one of these providers will collect and store the data provided during the order process. Both companies have very strict rules when it comes to processing personal information; please refer to the [Digital River Privacy Policy](https://www.digitalriver.com/corporate-policies/) respectively to the [Clickbank Privacy Policy](https://support.clickbank.com/hc/en-us/articles/115015510108-Privacy-Policies) for more information.

Birt Ltd. does not have access to the billing data related to your purchase (such as your credit card number or even the reason for a transaction failure). The only data that is recorded by Birt Ltd. in relation to each purchase is the email address and the name supplied during the ordering process as well as the purchase identifier assigned by the retailer. This data is used to provide access to the software and to technical support.

Both retailers may use cookies with a limited validity period for tracking affiliate purchases.

### Technical Support

All support requests are handled through Freshdesk and the data recorded by Freshdesk depends on the way your request is sent:

  * If your support request is sent by email, the message will be automatically processed by Freshdesk and your email address and the name configured in your email client will be recorded by Freshdesk.
  * If your support request is sent using the online form on the eareview.net website, the email address and the name provided in the form will be sent to and recorded by Freshdesk.
  * If your support request is sent by means of the installed Tick Data Suite support assistant, the email address specified in the application will be sent to and recorded by Freshdesk.

The above-mentioned data is only recorded by Freshdesk for the purposes of communicating with you and facilitating the assistance provided by Birt Ltd. support personnel.

If you choose to create a support account with Freshdesk the data you send is only recorded by Freshdesk and not by Birt Ltd.

Please see the Freshdesk [Data Protection & Commitment to GDPR](https://www.freshworks.com/privacy/gdpr/) for more information.

### Business Transfers

If Birt Ltd. or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Birt Ltd. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Birt Ltd. may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Birt Ltd. may change the Privacy Policy from time to time, in Birt Ltd.’s sole discretion. Visitors are encouraged to frequently check this page for any changes to the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the eareview.net website and the software provided on this website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](http://eareview.net/privacy-policy)
